neoretix.com 2010-12-30

# TubeHunter® - Download RedTube, Tube8, XTube, XVideos, xnxx, YouPorn, Youjizz, Megarotic, Red Tube, Pornhub, yuvutu, Spankwire, Maxporn, Pornorama, tnaflix, Pornotube, Dreammovies, Pornhost, Magicmovies, eskimotube, YouTube, Facebook, Myspace video

|  |  |   
---  

|   
---  
Neoretix Laboratory Privacy Policy  
We are committed to protecting your privacy and the security of information you provide to us. Neoretix Laboratory ("Neoretix") will not sell, rent, lease or disclose customer information to third parties unless required by law or unless you provide consent to such a disclosure. Other terms of Neoretix's privacy policy are as follows:   
   
Software Behavior   
Neoretix products do NOT have any spyware or adware. No personal information is collected, stored, or transmitted by Neoretix products. Neoretix products do NOT modify your web browser or registry. They do NOT install any browser plugins or hijackers.  
   
Trial Software Activation  
A valid e-mail address is required to receive trial unlock codes for many of our products. If you enter into a trial period of Neoretix software, and consent to our use of your e-mail address by providing the same, we may contact you via e-mail to provide additional information on our products and to survey you on your satisfaction with our software. We may also contact you to provide advance notice of termination of the trial period or an opportunity to extend your trial period. E-mail is our preferred method of communication and we value the privilege to use it.  
   
Product Purchasing  
Information we ask you to provide when purchasing or ordering will be only the information necessary to process your purchase or order. When fulfilling an order we will ask for your name, e-mail address, address (for shipping purposes), telephone number and credit card number, type and expiration date (if paying by credit card). We will use this information only for matters related to your order or product registration unless you request otherwise. Your credit card information will be maintained only for a period reasonably necessary to ensure payment has been received.  
   
Product Registration  
If, after or during purchase, you choose to register your Neoretix software, any information you provide will only be used to improve the service provided to you as a result of your registration. The details of information we gather will be used to uniquely identify your relationship to a Neoretix software application and potentially to support communication with you including: notification of software updates and service releases, notice of changes in policy that relate to the use of your software, and the provision to you of prioritized customer service or technical support.  
   
Security of Your Personal Information  
Neoretix takes the protection of the personal information you provide very seriously. Personal information collected is stored in password-controlled servers with limited access. When passing information over the Internet through the Neoretix service, information is protected through the use of encryption, specifically through the use of the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. However, perfect security on the Internet does not yet exist and we cannot warrant that our transfer of data is impenetrable or invulnerable to hackers. Internal data is shared through secured transmissions and maintained in secured databases. 

Neoretix may hire certain outside contractors to perform services or functions on our behalf (such as customer support, packaging & shipping). We will only provide those companies the personal information they need to complete the desired service. They are not permitted to use customer information for any other purpose and are obligated to keep your customer information confidential.

Information submitted to Neoretix may be transferred across national boundaries to or from our staff in other countries. Neoretix will only disclose information if required to do so by law, legal process or if in good faith it is deemed necessary for the public interest.  

Copyright © 1996 - 2010 by Neoretix Laboratory.  
All rights reserved.
